We've come to the bathroom in the morning.
I'm the new star of the show!
Sakura Kimo!
Congratulations!
So, this project will cover a quiz about me, Cocona Sakuragi
I would like to ask all of you here to answer the questions!
I'm tempted to show you who among the members knows the most about me!
I don't know!
This time, we have 3 people who have come forward and said that they are worthy of being the King of Sakuragi!
Thank you!
Woo hoo!
We have 3 people who love Cocona Sakuragi so much that they can't stop loving her!
They called me up and said, "Queue queue queue!
No, no, no.
They were in my Google calendar or something yesterday.
You know best!
No, I don't know about putting it on the Kurakon pillow!
I don't need to know. How about your enthusiasm, Mr. Nakayama?
What? Why am I here?
It's really bad!
Guess!
I'll guess with you too, Yuka?
That's why you're my senior.
You're a senior, aren't you?
Now, Nokki, how about you, Chikobo?
I don't know, I don't know at all.
I don't know. Everyone's so unmotivated.
Oh, oh, really...
Thank you very much.
Emma is the one with the cherry blossom in her last name.
It was written here.
The cherry blossom sisters.
Yes, the cherry blossom sisters.
Yes, ma'am.
We're going to win.
Yes, well, I understand your enthusiasm very well.
Hmmm...
So, let's get started! So, I would like to get started!
Yes!
Now, the first question!
Let's try it.
What?
No one?
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, I don't know anything about no one.
Okay, I'm going to ask Sakuragi some questions now. Here you go.
First, if you could take one thing to a deserted island, what would it be?
This is...
If you could take only one thing with you to a deserted island, here's the first question.
Imagine me as I was six months ago.
I was only 17.
I was 17 then. I'm 18 now.
I'm surprised at myself.
Surprised?
Looking back on it now, I feel that it is indeed surprising.
You said it, so I'm sure it's all surprising.
Is everyone all right then?
Yes, I'm fine.
Let's start with Ms. Nakayama.
Mr. Nakayama, please.
Friend.
I was going to write on my cell phone, but you said it was unexpected.
If one of my friends went, we could spend the rest of our lives having fun...
So, Tomo...
I see
Next, Mr. Kokubo
Gakuto.
If I could take him with me, I would.
Next, Mr. Sakurai
Live theater.
I like it.
I'm sure we can get a shot of it.
Certainly.
It's possible.
Yes, it is.
So what is the correct answer? So what is the correct answer?
If you could take only one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
I'll tell you what it would be.
Vaseline.
Why?
Because when my lips get dry.
When my lips get dry, they lose all their fat.
I tend to get down a lot.
I can't travel.
I'm going to take some Vaseline with me.
I want to make sure that I have it with me and that I can put it down properly.
Also, I think Vaseline is useful in case of a fire or something.
I'm also thinking that Vaseline will be useful in case of a fire or something.
I think Vaseline is very important.
I think Vaseline is definitely important.
Wassu
This line is
It was Vaseline!
So, that's a shame!
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
Surely all the downer energy comes from the lips?
From the lips maybe
At this point in my life, when I lose water.
I'd get really stuck.
Hey.
Can you move?
I don't think so now.
Let's move on to the second question.
Let's continue.
How are you doing?
The second question!
What?
What did I say to that?
Please answer me.Please answer
I wrote.
Already early.
I've been seen so much.
This is...
I don't understand the question at first.
They're taking advantage of you, aren't they?
No, I don't.
Oh, you're saying...
That's kind of cute.
Did you write it?
What's your answer, Mr. Nakayama?
Let's just go with the flow and call it a jar.
If you don't do it, it'll happen.
I see.
Kokubo-san, please.
Yes, Happy
Oh!
I see.
Next, Mr. Sakurai
Yes.
You look like him.
But you're from that side of the family.
I know, so let's see the answer.
How are you doing?
Please.
If you were a piece of stationery, what would you be?
Third question! If you were a piece of stationery, what would you be?
Yes!
It's easy!
Okay, okay!
Mariko.
How did you know?
Don't get my name wrong.
Mariko!
You're early!
Okay, okay. Okay, okay, okay.
You got it? Are you sure now?
I'm sure.
Yes, I do.
How about you, Yuna?
I don't.
No, I don't.
You always have none.
Let's start with you, Ms. Nakayama.
Corpus in terms of softness.
Oh, no.
Yes, you're right.
No, it's not. Next, Yuna-san, please.
Yes, color ten.
Mr. Sakurai, I'm corpus too.
Correct answer, please.
If you were a piece of stationery, what would you be?
Stationery?
What did I have for stationery?
I haven't studied at all. I can't think of any stationery.
Yes, you're right.
Three-color ballpoint pens.
If I use a mechanical pencil, it will break easily.
I don't have the heart to break that easily.
It's a ballpoint pen with a proper lead.
And it has three colors! Red for passion, blue for calm.
From the three-colored ballpoint pen that I've been bumping and scraping the money out of.
I see...
The answer is a tri-color ballpoint pen.
That's very close!
But now I would have said "compass" for sure.
But at this time, this is a three-color ballpoint pen.
We all answered incorrectly!
You're so close!
Do you know what a compass is?
If I had the knowledge, I'd call it a compass.
If I had the knowledge...
If I had knowledge.Indeed.
I didn't think of it at the time.
So let's go to the fourth question.
Question 4.
How long have you been a boy?
What is your male history?
I think you know this one, don't you?
The fourth question, men's history.
Men's history?
How old are you now?
I'm 18 now, but I was 17 when I was here.
I've done a lot of interviews and talked about this in magazines.
I'm sure you can guess.
Oh, everyone!
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow!
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
It's totally ripped.
Did you get it? Now, question four.
What's your male period? Mr. Nakayama, please.
Thirteen years.
You mean 13 years at this time?
And from the age of 4 years old.
I see. Mr. Kokubo, please.
He said he had red hair for 12 years.
I see.
Next, Mr. Sakai.
About 6 years?
I've been doing it since I was in the 5th grade.
Let's see your answer.
What about the male period?
The male period is 10 years.
Ten years.
Ten years, gentlemen.
That's what you've been telling your sister since you were 7 years old.
That was close. That was close.
Well, you've been doing it for 10 years.
I'd like to challenge myself at different times.I'd like to try different times of the year.
Okay, 0.5 points.
I won't go in.
I'm not going in.
I've been doing this since I was six.
I'm sorry, gentlemen.
Too bad.
I haven't hit anyone yet.
Because, I don't know, there's a lot of flippant sentiment after that.
That's what I've been told, but...
Well, I was hoping the male period would be a success.
That's amazing.
When you're born, you're on your own.
Now, let's go to the fifth question.
What's your favorite salad dressing?
Wow, that's a tough one.
Which one?
What's your favorite salad dressing? Please answer.
Wow, I don't know.
Favorite salad dressing at this time? Yes, I wonder.
But it hasn't changed. It's still the same.
I get this when I'm catering.
You mean the kind they have at the caterer?
There must be. There is. There is. Sometimes there is, sometimes there isn't.
Watch out, I don't eat salad.
Okay, let's hear your answer, Mr. Nakayama. Yes, sir.
Yes. Bolinho oil and salt.
Did you think of that? I thought it looked stylish.
Then, Ms. Koma, please.
Onion.
But I used to hate onions.
Onions.
I hate green onions, but onions...
I don't care anymore.
Next, Mr. Yama!
Sesame oil
Sesame oil and salt?
Salt?Salt?
You use salt with each other?
Sesame oil and salt is delicious. It's delicious.
Is there a world in here?
Maybe.
I don't know.
What's your favorite salad dressing?
Uh...
Yuzu-flavored Japanese dressing.
First of all, there's a big difference between yuzu and no yuzu.
How refreshing is it?
This is something I used to do when I was catering for a live performance of EBICHU.
I always used to use aojiso dressing when it was served at the catering for the live concerts.
But when I came across the yuzu-flavored Japanese dressing, I thought it was fate.
Wow!
The correct answer was yuzu-flavored Japanese dressing.
We have it, don't we, in catering?
Yes, we do.
You should try it.
How many?
Eight, so three to go.
Oh, no.
Say something.
It's not an individual game. It's a team game.
Let's go to the sixth question.
Go on.
What made you happy recently?
What has made you happy lately?
I'm talking about something.
What made you happy recently?
Do you have a hint?
What kind of hints? What kind of hints? What kind of hints?
Friends.
About my personal life.
When you feel happy.
I'm a private person, mom.
Mother? And I did something Mother? And I did something.
Oh. Sixth question, what made you happy recently? Mr. Nakayama.
Shopping. Yeah.
Going out. Yeah.
Going out
Kokubo-san I played with my mother.
Played with my mom Next, Sakurai-san
Saw a movie with my mom
Did you go shopping or have fun?
Then, please tell us.
What made you happy recently?
What made me happy recently?
Look at this dress.
Tadaan.
Isn't it cute?
I love it. I bought this.
I bought this dress for the Skeletal Wave Awards.
It's a little rough here.
It's got a little bit of a tighter waist.
The legs are a little...
Mr. Wave is a little bit...
The legs are a bit tight...
I was a little tense, but I found a dress that covered it up well.
I met this dress when I went shopping with my parents, and I love it so much, and I bought it recently, which ended up being a point of overjoyedness.
I bought my favorite outfit, which is the right thing to do, but shopping is OK.
Go play with your mother.
I didn't go to play. I went shopping.
That's playing.
I was a little too abstract.
Tanaka-san is the best shopper.
I bought it!
Question 7.
Next...
What's your favorite time of day?
7th question, what is your favorite time of day?
It hasn't changed that much.
You mean morning, noon and night?
I like to do this at night. I like to do this at night.
All right, all right.
Mr. Nakayama, please.
Time to look at your phone.
Like TikTok or Dunsta before night.
I think I like to watch TikTok and Dunsta.
Mr. Kita.
Ask him.
Ooh.
That's good.
Skin Care
Ooh.
A pack?
Cute.
Okay, let's hear your answer.
What is your favorite time of day?
Favorite time of day?
This one.
This is my favorite time.
It's something about my
body
It's like it's making me
I like to see my body
this...
this.
Whew.
This kind of time is
In my opinion
I love it.
Aaah!
Get mad!
Oh!
Correct!
One point for everyone!
Finally. Finally.
What do you think?
How does it feel to get a point for the seventh question?
I don't know, it just keeps going and going and going.
My hair is getting blah as the video goes on.
The tension at this point is a little weird.
What did you do?
What did I do?
The eighth and last question.
Oh no! The last one.
Question 8, please.
What's the eighth question?
How many questions?
I mean, you're probably not counting.
No, I didn't.
I don't know.
Okay, let's go.
Yuko.
Like the 10th question?
Oh, you mean you're about to say that?
YUNO-chan
The 10th question.
Yama-chan
Question 13.
Answers, please.
How many questions are you on?
How many?
I'm pretty sure I didn't count.
Vamo's.
Oh, my God.
This is question 10.
Wow.
Am I right?
Is it right?
It's not right, but it's right.
Is this one right?
Is it there? Is this one right?
Yes!
Yeah!
I see.
2 points for Yunotoriko!
Got it!
At that time, I thought it was the 10th question.
I thought I got it right, but it was the 8th question.
So...
All the questions are done.
Let's see the points.
Nakayama got 2 points.
Kokoko-san has 2 points.
Ema-san has
Zero.
0 points
So, the 1st Sakura Gyo-ou is
Janken (rock-paper-scissors-scissors game)
first and rock-paper-scissors point
Ah!
Here you go!
I laughed.
Too light.
Too light!
So, the 1st Sakura Gyo
Yu no
Oh!
Indeed
Winner.
I like it.
Let's have today's winner, Kokoko, comment!
Please do.
I thought rock-paper-scissors was very strong these days.
There were no serious questions.
Questions are questions, too.
The way you answered, the way you answered...The way you answered and the way I answered.
Both of them seemed to be in a great groove.
So, this was Sakura Gyo.
Finally, let's listen to
Let's hear how Sakuragyo answers!
Is there any question you want us to guess for sure?
A question you definitely want me to guess?
I've said this before, but it was in the male period.
No one guessed it.
I think I know now what the male period is and what your favorite time of day is.
All 10 of you?
Ten.
Nine. I think I know all nine.
I hope you were all able to answer that.
Well, I hope so.
I hope so.
This is all I have left.
What are you doing?
If you could answer me, I think it would be great to see you again.
I'd love to.
I'm going to quickly answer the last question.
I'm going to ask you a question that I hope you'll be able to guess from this VCR.
I didn't get it right. How about you?
Well, you guessed two questions, so that's good.
You already guessed two, didn't you?
What?
You just guessed them in rock-paper-scissors-scissors. They're almost the same.
That's true.
You can always tell, Mr. White.
Thank you.
Oh!
It changes every day.
Daily? Different day.
You got zero questions. How did you do?
Were you disappointed?
Yes, it was.
I thought our minds were similar.
That's true. That's true.
But since it was zero.
I'd like to learn more about Sakuragiyo.
Oh! That went well.
Thank you for your best comment.
So, everyone, please continue to like
Please keep liking Kotona Sakurai!
That's all! You have liked Kotona Sakurai!
That's all!
Subscribe to our channel!
Good Button!
Comment!
Thank you very much!
And please keep the switch on!
That's all for Sakura Gear!
Bye-bye!